A Guide to the Papers of James Washington Singleton 1770-1975
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Photographs
  - Photographic Prints
    - Lily Singleton Thomas Osburn (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Nelson and Barbara Osburn (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Clara Singleton Patty (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Paxton (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Cabel St. Clair (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Singleton Coat of Arms (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Ed Singleton (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 31)
    - James W. Singleton (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Jonett P. Singleton (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Cora Elder Thomas (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Francis W. Thomas, Jr. (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Parthenia M. Thomas (deLoach) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 36)
    - W. F. Thorton (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Mrs. Humphrey Ward (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Judith Ball Thomas Wysong (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Prints, Sketches and Lithographs
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 41)
- Oversize Newspapers (Box Oversize Newspaper Box)
  - District of Columbia
    - National Intelligencer April 26, 1827 December 18, 1828
    - The Washington Post October 10, 1928 January 21, 1936 December 13, 1936
    - The Washington Star October 21, 1923 February 21, 1926 October 14, 1928
  - Georgia
    - Atlanta American October 23, 1932
  - Illinois
    - Adams County Democrat October 28, 1882
    - The Chicago Times September 28, 1876 December 26, 1885
    - The Highland Park Press March 1, 1923
    - Daily Quincy Herald November 5, 1878 August 3, 1882 May 30, 1919
    - Quincy Daily Whig August 10, 1882 August 13, 1882 August 18, 1882
  - Baltimore, Maryland
    - American Farmer April 12, 1822 April 26, 1822 November 15, 1822 August 1, 1828 May 7, 1830 July 16, 1830
    - The Baltimore Sun April 30, 1889 January 9, 1891 May 1, 1891 July 20, 1891 July 21, 1891 July 22, 1891 December 7, 1892 May 11, 1894 January 17, 1895 February 9, 1930 April 6, 1930
  - New York
    - New York American and Journal June 29, 1902
    - New York Daily News July 27, 1864 December 8, 1864 November 20, 1932
    - New York Times August 6, 1922 February 12, 1928
  - Ohio
    - Cleveland Plain Dealer November 9, 1892 November 9, 1932
    - Columbus Dispatch December 30, 1923
  - Pennsylvania
    - Gettysburg Compiler March 27, 1868
    - Saturday Evening Post (Philadelphia) November 29, 1924
  - Tennessee
    - Daily Memphis Avalanche May 3, 1868
  - Virginia
    - Virginia Free Press (Charlestown) March 13, 1845 September 15, 1900
    - Virginian Herald (Fredericksburg) December 13, 1875
    - The Genius of Liberty (Leesburg) March 4, 1817
    - Lynchburg News January 5, 1892 January 14, 1892
    - Richmond Whig March 26, 1861 March 14, 1865
    - Winchester Virginia January 2, 1861
  - West Virginia
    - Farmers Advocate October 29, 1910
    - Martinsburg Evening Journal March 2, 1929
    - Miscellaneous Central Presbyterian